Knolls Action Project; Records apap105
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Department of Energy (DOE), 1973-1994; 4; 2.0 cubic ft.
  - DOE: Rocky Flats, 1988; 1992-1993 (Box 2 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 13)
    Includes Citizen's Guide to Rocky Flats published by the Rocky Mountain Peace Center.
  - DOE: Savannah River Plant, 1988; 1991-1993 (Box 2 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 14)
    Clippings. Also includes a GAO report on Nuclear Materials: Nuclear arsenal reductions allow consideration of tritium production options.
  - DOE: Sequoyah, 1991 (Box 2 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 15)
    Clipping regarding suspension of plant official.
  - DOE: Waste Isolation Pilot Plant, 1990-1992 (Box 2 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 16)
    Includes clippings, fact sheets, and GAO testimony on Nuclear Waste: Issues affecting land withdrawal of DOE's Waste Isolation Pilot Project.
  - DOE: Yucca Mountain, 1991-1994 (Box 2 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 17)
    Includes clippings, copies of Nevada Nuclear Waste News, GAO testimonies on nuclear waste and Yucca Mountain Project, and GAO Report on Nuclear Waste: Yucca Mountain project behind schedule and facing major scientific uncertainties.
  - DOE Chief: Hazel O'Leary, 1993 (Box 2 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 18)
    Questions and answers for Secretary-Designate of Energy Hazel O'Leary, from the Senate Energy and Natural Resources Committee.
  - 20/20 Vision, [Undated] (Box 2 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 19)
  - Environmental Defense Institute (INEL News), 1991-1992 (Box 2 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 20)
    Includes a Citizens guide to the Idaho National Engineering Laboratory compiled for the Environmental Defense Institute.
  - Research (Karl Francis), [Undated] (Box 2 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 21)
    Seminar project of Karl Francis.
  - Research on KAPL, 1973-1974; 1979-1982; 1986-1987 (Box 2 (4-Department of Energy (DOE)), Folder 22)
- Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and other publications, 1956-1992; 1997; 5; 4.0 cubic ft.
  This series includes miscellaneous reports and legal documentation. Box 1 contains GAO Reports, DEC and DOE publications. Box 2 contains several annual DOE Environmental Restoration and Waste Management Five-Year Plans. Box 2 also contains several books and publications prepared by organizations and authored by individuals advocating disarmament and economic conversion. The publications in Boxes 1 and 2 are listed in the order they can be found in the boxes. Box 3 contains copies of reports and surveys, some dating as far back as 1956. Some copies are of poor quality and difficult to read or determine the date. Some of the documents were obtained through FOIA requests.
  - Final Environmental Impact Statement on the Disposal of the S3G and D1G Prototype Reactor Plants, 1997 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 1)
  - NYS: Energy Research and Development Authority, 1991-1992; reports (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 2)
  - Reports, 1989; 1991 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 3)
    "Cleanup or Coverup? Confidential briefing paper concerning the Knolls Atomic Power Lab", prepared by the Government Accountability Project; GAO Report Nuclear Health and Safety: Environmental, Health, and Safety Practices at Naval Reactors Facilities.
  - U.S. Department of Transportation (DOT) Guides, 1988; 1990; 1992 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 4)
    Guides prepared by DOT regarding hazardous materials.
  - Citizens Environmental Coalition - A citizens' guide to understanding measurements of toxic and radioactive concentrations, 1990 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 1)
  - The Legislative Commission on Critical Transportation Choices - Dangerous Cargo! The transportation of hazardous materials by highway: an analysis of federal and state regulations aimed at minimizing risk, with legislative recommendations for New York State, 1993 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 2)
  - Community Teamwork: Working together to promote hazardous materials transportation safety (DOT, 1983) (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 3)
  - GAO Report -World Agriculture: Factors influencing trends in world agricultural production and trade, 1989 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 4)
  - GAO Report - Reports and Testimony, 1991 March (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 5)
    Highlights: Deposit insurance; Federally sponsored research; Tax administration.
  - GAO Report - Reports and Testimony, 1991 April (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 5)
    Highlights: Banking; Bottled water; Health care costs.
  - GAO Report - Reports and Testimony, 1991 June (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 6)
    Highlights: Resolution Trust Corp.; Canadian health care; 1990 census.
  - GAO Report -Asbestos Removal and Disposal: EPA needs to improve compliance with its regulations, 1992 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 7)
  - GAO Report -Nuclear Science: Monitoring improved, but more planning needed for DOE test and research reactors, 1992 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 8)
  - GAO Report -Defense Procurement: Trends for 1985-93 in DOD's spending, employment, and contractors, 1992 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 9)
  - GAO Report -Navy Strategic Forces: Trident II proceeding toward deployment, 1988 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 10)
  - GAO Report -Navy Maintenance: Fewer shipyards may be needed as ship repair requirements decline, 1992 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 11)
  - GAO Report -Navy Ships: Plans and anticipated liabilities to terminate SSN-21 program contracts, 1992 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 12)
  - GAO Report -Navy Research: Status of programs in nonacoustic antisubmarine warfare research, 1991 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 13)
  - GAO Report -1992 Navy Budget: Potential reductions in research, development, test, and evaluation programs, 1991 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 14)
  - GAO Report -1993 Navy Budget: Potential reductions and rescissions in RDT&E programs, 1992 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 15)
  - GAO Report -1993 Navy Budget: Potential reductions in weapons procurement programs, 1992 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 16)
  - GAO Report -Navy ACQ=Development of the AN/BSY-1 combat system, 1992 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 17)
  - GAO Report -Navy ACQ=AN/BSY-1 combat system operational evaluation, 1992 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 18)
  - GAO Report -Submarine Combat System: BSY-2 development risks must be addressed and production schedule reassessed, 1991 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 19)
  - GAO Report -Submarine Combat System: Technical challenges confronting Navy's Seawolf AN/BSY-2 development, 1989 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 20)
  - GAO Report -Navy Torpedo Program: MK-48 ADCAP propulsion system upgrade not needed, 1992 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 21)
  - GAO Report -Submarine Technology: Transition plans needed to realize gains from DOD advanced research, 1990 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 22)
  - GAO Report -Nuclear Health and Safety: DOE needs to take further actions to ensure safe transportation of radioactive materials, 1988 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 23)
  - GAO Report -Undersea Surveillance: Navy continues to build ships designed for Soviet threat, 1992 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 24)
  - DEC - 1987 NYS Low-Level Radioactive Waste Transportation Report, 1989 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 25)
  - DEC - 1988 NYS Low-Level Radioactive Waste Transportation Report, 1991 April (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 26)
  - DEC - 1989 NYS Low-Level Radioactive Waste Transportation Report, 1991 July (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 27)
  - DEC - Risk assessment and financial surety requirements analysis for transportation of Low-level radioactive waste in New York State, Volume II (draft, 1988) (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 28)
  - DEC - Final Generic Environmental Impact Statement for Promulgation of 6 NYCRR Part 381: Regulations for Low-level radioactive waste transporter permit and manifest system, Volume I, 1988 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 29)
  - New York State Commission on Judicial Conduct, Annual Report, 1990 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 30)
  - U.S. DOT - Annual Report on Hazardous Materials Transportation, 1990 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 31)
  - Educational Series from DOE on Science, Society, and America's Nuclear Waste, 1992 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 32)
  - The Nairobi forward - looking strategies for the advancement of women, 1985 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 33)
  - U.S. DOE -Environmental Restoration and Waste Management Five-Year Plan, Student Edition, 1992 (Box 1 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 34)
  - U.S. DOE -Nuclear Weapons Complex Reconfiguration Study, 1991 (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 35)
  - U.S. DOE -Final Environmental Impact Statement: Special Isotope Separation Project, Idaho National Engineering Laboratory, Idaho Falls, Idaho (Volumes 1 and 1, 1988) (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 36)
  - U.S. DOE -Environmental Restoration and Waste Management Five-Year Plan (FY 1991-1995) (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 37)
  - U.S. DOE -Response to public comments on FY 1991-1995 Environmental Restoration and Waste Management Five-Year Plan and Draft Applied Research, Development, Demonstration, Testing, and Evaluation Plan, 1989 (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 38)
  - U.S. DOE -Environmental Restoration and Waste Management Five - Year Plan FY 1992-1996, 1990 (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 39)
  - U.S. DOE -Environmental Restoration and Waste Management Five - Year Plan FY 1993-1997, 1991 (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 40)
  - The Helpless Giant: a metaportrait of the defense budget with an essay by Andrew Hamilton and introduction by Congressman Les Aspin, 1972 (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 41)
  - Seymour Melman -An Economic Alternative to the Arms Race: Conversion from military to civilian economy, 1987 (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 42)
  - Despair and Empowerment Workshops - Despairwork: awakening to the peril and promise of our time (Joanna Macy) a pamphlet, [Undated] (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 43)
  - Worldwatch Institute -Reassessing Nuclear Power: The fallout from Chernobyl, 1987 (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 44)
  - Congressional Joint Economic Committee -Economics of Defense Policy: ADM. H.G. Rickover (Part 1), 1982 January 28 (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 45)
  - Association for Transarmament Studies -National Security through Civilian-Based Defense (Gene Sharp), 1985 (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 46)
  - American Friends Service Committee -Questions and Answers on the Soviet Threat and National Security, 1981 (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 47)
  - Institute for Policy Studies -The Counterforce Syndrome: A guide to U.S. nuclear weapons and strategic doctrine (Robert Aldridge), 1978) (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 48)
  - The Council on Economic Priorities -The Costs and Consequences of Reagan's Military Buildup: A report to The International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers, AFL-CIO and The Coalition for a New Foreign and Military Policy, 1982 (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 49)
  - Concerning Dissent and Civil Disobedience (Abe Fortas), 1968) (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 50)
  - Is it Too Late? The longest letter I've ever written. (Taeko Kansha), 1987) (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 51)
  - Women Working for a Nuclear Free and Independent Pacific -Pacific Women Speak, 1987 (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 52)
  - What if Nobody Came? (Dorice McDaniels), 1984) (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 53)
  - Alternative Defense Project -An Emerging Consensus: Common security through qualitative disarmament, 1988 (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 54)
  - Investor Responsibility Research Center -The Nuclear Weapons Industry (Kenneth Bertsch and Linda Shaw), 1984) (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 55)
  - Institute for Policy Studies -The Federal Budget and Social Reconstruction (Marcus Raskin), 1978) (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 56)
  - The Boston Study Group -The Price of Defense: A new strategy for military spending, 1979 (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 57)
  - Economic Conversion: Revitalizing America's economy (edited by Suzanne Gordon and Dave McFadden), 1984) (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 58)
  - World Military and Social Expenditures (Ruth Leger Sivard), 1983 (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 59)
  - Institute for Policy Studies -You Can't Hug with Nuclear Arms!, 1982 (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 60)
    Photos from June 12 and related disarmament demonstrations.
  - The ACCESS Resource Guide: An international directory of information on war, peace, and security (edited by William Kincade and Priscilla Hayner), 1988) (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 61)
  - Pasos Hacia la Paz Interior (in Spanish), Undated (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 62)
  - Peace Pilgrim: Her life and work in her own words, 1982 (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 63)
  - PlanetHood: The key to your survival and prosperity Benjamin Ferencz and Ken Keyes, Jr., 1988 (Box 2 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 64)
  - 100 Recent Findings of Historic Contamination, 1984; 1987 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 1)
  - Afftrex Protest, 1987-1988 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 2)
  - Appeal, 1989; 1992 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 3)
    An appeal of a determination issued by the Office of Naval Reactors (of the DOE) that denied a request for information as pursuant to the FOIA.
  - CERCLA, 1986 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 4)
    Includes a report on the status of the KAPL implementation of the DOE Comprehensive Environmental Response, Compensation and Liability Act (CERCLA).
  - Chemical Wash Disposal, 1958; 1961; 1979 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 5)
  - Cyanide-Knolls site, 1986 January 13 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 6)
  - Documents, 1967; 1970; 1986; 1989 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 7)
    Documents relating to CERCLA; evaluation of the Knolls site radioactive liquid waste annual discharge limit; DOE's Personnel Security Assurance Program.
  - Documents, 1985; 1987-1988 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 8)
    Documents relating to Knolls site radioactive contamination; Gag Order; appeal of FOIA response.
  - Environmental Assessment: Installation and Operation of the AF Reactor Prototype in the S8G Prototype Plant, 1991 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 9)
  - Evidence of Radiation Contamination, 1956; 1979; 1987 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 10)
  - External Dosimetry/Internal Monitoring - KAPL, 1987 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 11)
  - FOI Originals, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 12)
    Correspondence regarding requests for information; also includes the following requested document: "Knolls Atomic Power Laboratory Audit of Environmental Programs" dated June 8, 1987.
  - FOIA, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 13)
    Includes requests to John H. Carter, Chief of FOIA and Privacy Acts, DOE, and a list of "Worthwhile KAPL documents to FOI".
  - FOIA, 1988-1992 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 14)
    Correspondence regarding requests for information.
  - For Pat, 1987; 1989 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 15)
    Correspondence related to the radiological survey of the Mohawk River sediment.
  - Gag Order Suit, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 16)
    First amended complaint and defendants' answer filed in U.S. District Court.
  - Geohydrologic Report - KAPL Sanitary Landfill (Niskayuna), 1978-1979 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 17)
  - Geohydrologic Report - Sanitary Landfill (Milton), 1978-1979 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 18)
  - Industrial Safety, Incident Prevention and Industrial Hygiene Appraisal of the KSO and follow-up, 1985-1986 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 19)
  - GE documents, 1956; 1967; 1979; 1985(?); 1987-1988 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 20)
  - KAPL and environmental studies, 1966-1967; 1980; 1986-1989 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 21)
  - KAPL Documents, 1988; 1990-1992 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 22)
  - KAPL Internal - 61 Radiological Contaminated Sites, 1985 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 23)
  - KAPL Parking lot/Memo, 1985; 1988 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 24)
    Documents related to soil contamination at KAPL parking lot.
  - Knolls Soil and Water Monitoring, 1984 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 25)
  - Landfill - Knolls, 1980-1982; 1988 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 26)
  - Mohawk River 1, 1989 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 27)
  - Mohawk River 2, 1978; 1980; 1987 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 28)
  - Peek Street, 1989 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 29)
    Documents related to contamination at the original Knolls site.
  - Preliminary Assessment 2, (4/88), 1986; 1988 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 30-31)
    Assessments reports at various sites.
  - SNR Appraisals - Quality (Assurance calibration: Mechanical calibration operation), 1985; 1988 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 32)
    Reports of Schenectady Naval Reactors (SNR).
  - SPRU Facilities (Separations Processing Research Unit), 1972; 1976; 1983-1984; 1989 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 33)
  - Schenectady Gazette Blowout, 1989; clippings (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 34)
  - Slurry Drum Survey, 1982 December (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 35)
  - Soil Survey - former rail shipping area (Knolls site), (February 27, 1984), 1989 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 36)
  - Weston Geophysical, [Undated] (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 37)
  - Windsor Site, 1978; 1985 (Box 3 (5-Government Reports (GAO, DEC, DOE) and ), Folder 38)
- Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1975-1994; 6; 3.4 cubic ft.
  This series contains information on miscellaneous subjects. Boxes 1 through 3 contain folders that are filed alphabetically. Among the prominent subjects, Box 1 contains documentation related to health and safety issues at KAPL sites. Box 2 contains information on naval shipyards and submarines. There is an extensive file on the Seawolf submarine. Box 3 includes testimony from the December 1990 hearing, environmental assessment, and documents relating to the AFR/NRDC lawsuit regarding the proposed installation and operation of the Advanced Fleet Reactor prototype at Kesselring site (1990-1992). Box 4 includes an extensive clipping file on GE and its issues (community relations, union, strikes).
  - Briefing Book on the Military-Industrial Complex, [Undated] (Box 1 (6-Miscellaneous Subject Files), Folder 1)
    Published by Council for a Livable World Education Fund.
  - Chernobyl, 1991 (Box 1 (6-Miscellaneous Subject Files), Folder 2)
    Articles from the New York Times on the aftermath of Chernobyl.
  - Clippings, 1989-1991 (Box 1 (6-Miscellaneous Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Conversion Campaign Update, [Undated] (Box 1 (6-Miscellaneous Subject Files), Folder 4)
    Unidentified article.
  - Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 1 (6-Miscellaneous Subject Files), Folder 5)
    Correspondence from KAP to Governor Mario Cuomo, Congressman Michael McNulty, and Philip Salm, Manager SNR regarding radioactive contamination.
  - DEC: Mohawk River Study, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (6-Miscellaneous Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - "Deadly Deception" (INFACT), 1991 (Box 1 (6-Miscellaneous Subject Files), Folder 7)
    Video expose of GE. Includes an organizing packet for GE boycott.
  - First Strike/Trident II, 1978; 1980-1987 (Box 1 (6-Miscellaneous Subject Files), Folder 8)
    Articles and information on nuclear weapons.
    See oversize box for "War and Peace in the Nuclear Age" (Special Section to the Boston Globe, October 17, 1982), The New Generation of Nuclear Weapons (NARMIC).
  - Floating Reactors: The Secret Story of Nuclear Power at Sea (Greenpeace), [Undated] (Box 1 (6-Miscellaneous Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Food Irradiation, 1992 (Box 1 (6-Miscellaneous Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - KAPL: GAO Report and Testimony, 1991 (Box 1 (6-Miscellaneous Subject Files), Folder 11)
    Environmental, Health and Safety Practices at Naval Reactors Facilities.
  - KAPL: Savannah River Site (SRS) Waste Cycle, 1992 (Box 1 (6-Miscellaneous Subject Files), Folder 12)
    Includes the following report prepared for DOE: Savannah River Site Interim Waste Management Program Plan, FY 1991-1992.
  - KAPL: Niskayuna LLWTF EA (Low level Waste Treatment Facility - Environmental Assessment), 1993 (Box 1 (6-Miscellaneous Subject Files), Folder 13)
    Includes the following report prepared by DOE Office of Naval Reactors: Environmental Assessment: Construction and operation of the Knolls site low level radioactive material processing facility.
  - KAPL: Niskayuna Site, 1982; 1988-1994 (Box 1 (6-Miscellaneous Subject Files), Folder 14)
    Primarily clippings from 1989; also information about activities at KAPL sent by James Burn (KAPL) to Daniel Mackay (1993).
  - KAPL: Peek Street Temporary Atomic Power Laboratory (TAPL) Site, 1975; 1979; 1988-1993 (Box 1 (6-Miscellaneous Subject Files), Folder 15)
    Includes documents received from DOE in response to FOI request by Thomas Carpenter of the Government Accountability Project.
  - KAPL: West Milton Site, 1991-1993 (Box 1 (6-Miscellaneous Subject Files), Folder 16)